scanmedios.com 2009-02-23

# About Us

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES.

This Privacy Policy outlines the information gathering, use and dissemination practices for this Web site, mediosone.com. From time to time, we may update or modify our Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy, as modified, will govern our information gathering, use and dissemination practices. Modifications will apply to information acquired by mediosone.com either before or after the time of such modification. If at any time you do not want your information used in the manner described in the then current Privacy Policy, you should unsubscribe from our list and not provide us with any further information.

How this Privacy Policy applies to you.

mediosone.com is a direct marketer that delivers targeted messages to its members. You are a member of the mediosone.com community (a ÒMemberÓ) and this policy governs how we gather, use and disseminate information about you if one of the following applies:

You have requested or agreed via this Web site to receive e-mails and information by providing us with your e-mail address and/or other information; You have requested or agreed to receive e-mails and information from one our Partners; or You have received an e-mail from us notifying you that mediosone.com has received your e-mail address and/or other information from a permission based third party and you have not unsubscribed or opted out of the mediosone.com service in the manner described in the e-mail.

As a Member, we will provide you with e-mail from mediosone.com and/or its advertisers, affiliates, third party marketers, merchants, and strategic alliance partners (ÒPartnersÓ) regarding new releases, entertainment, prizes, surveys, products and special offers. If you do not want your information used in the manner permitted by this Privacy Policy, you may choose at any time to not be contacted or have your information shared by canceling your mediosone.com membership. This is accomplished by sending an e-mail with your request to webmaster@mediosone.com, or by unsubscribing to a mediosone.com e-mail by following the instructions contained at the end of each e-mail. In order for you to remove your information from our Partners' databases, you may need to contact the Partner directly.

Information From Children.

We do not provide services to children, nor is this Web site directed towards children. If you are under 18, you may not subscribe to mediosone.com services. Moreover, we will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the ChildrenÕs Online Privacy Protection Act (ÒCOPPAÓ).

What information may mediosone.com collect from you?

mediosone.com may gather personally identifiable information about Members (such as name, postal address, e-mail address, gender, date of birth, interests, other demographic information). This information may be gathered any time such information is included in any form of communication with us, or in any interaction with the mediosone.com Web site.

What are cookies, web bugs and web beacons and how does mediosone.com use them?

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, many Web sites use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Web bugs and web beacons are technologies that assist service providers in determining who has seen their ads. We may use cookies, web bugs, web beacons or other new technologies in the future. You may learn more about these terms and the associated technology by visiting www.netlingo.com.

How does mediosone.com and its Partners use your information?

mediosone.com AND ITS PARTNERS MAY USE YOUR INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE AS DETERMINED IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION. Without limiting the foregoing, we may share or sell your personally identifiable information with our Partners for their direct and online marketing purposes. Though we are selective as to whom we partner with and endeavor to work with partners with similar policies and practices, we do not control the policies and practices of our Partners, and it is possible that they will use your personal information in a manner which is inconsistent with this privacy policy, and they may not provide the opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe from their service.

In addition, we may release your information to a third party in the event that: we believe that the membership is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts; we are required to disclose the information pursuant to a subpoena, court order or administrative order; some or all of our operations, stock or assets are sold or otherwise transferred; or we otherwise deem such release necessary or appropriate.

We may enhance or merge your personally identifiable information with data collected from other sources to use in direct or online marketing, including the data services described on this Web site. All information provided to us by a Member may be used to support our marketing and data services businesses and those of our Partners. These services include the provision of and use of personally identifiable data to marketing companies, advertising agencies, data compilers, data companies, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference and look-up service programs. We may use your information to provide services for others in the nature of direct marketing applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation.

We send e-mail to individuals who have agreed on our Web site to receive e-mail from us or to individuals who have agreed on third party Web sites to receive e mail from third parties such as mediosone.com. As a result, laws requiring particular information or certain formatting for unsolicited commercial e-mail are not applicable to our messages.

NOTWITHSTANDING ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THIS POLICY, WE MAY SELL OR TRANSFER YOUR INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION.

How does mediosone.com protect your personal information?

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. This site does not use security encryption measures. Therefore, information that you disclose by use of this site (as with any site that is non-secure), by posting a message or using e-mail, potentially could be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties or use of such information by third parties for their own purposes, legal or illegal. As a result, mediosone.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Moreover, because of the global nature of the Internet, when you give us information, that information may be sent electronically to servers outside of the country where you originally entered the information.

What else do you need to know about your privacy and this policy?

The web pages at http://www.mediosone.com and some of the e-mail sent by mediosone.com contain links to external sites beyond our control. mediosone.com can not represent or guarantee that such sites have privacy policies similar to our own. Please review the privacy statement of any site linked from mediosone.com prior to providing such site with your information.

Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to or use of the Web site, your use of our services, or to our handling, use or disclosure of your information, shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in Marin County, California. However, if we believe you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any appropriate court. You consent to jurisdiction and venue in such courts located in Marin County, California. Any arbitration under this agreement shall be conducted under the prevailing rules of the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration with respect to this Web site shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php)

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique ÒcookieÓ on your browser.

WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO UPDATE THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME, SO YOU SHOULD REVIEW THIS POLICY FREQUENTLY.

If you have any questions regarding the policies of this site or your dealings with this site, please send e-mail to webmaster@mediosone.com
